<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Noticias ahora</title>
		<link>https://www.europapress.es</link>
		<description>Noticias de actualidad</description>
		<language>es-ES</language>
		<item>
			<title>L’Europa non si fa influenzare dalle paure delle Borse asiatiche e procede cauta ma positiva</title>
			<link>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/leuropa-non-si-fa-influenzare-dalle-paure-delle-borse-asiatiche-e-procede-cauta-ma-positiva/</link>
			<dc:creator>
			<![CDATA[ Rossana Prezioso ]]>
			</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2022 00:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<category>
			<![CDATA[ Economia e Mercati ]]>
			</category>
			<category>
			<![CDATA[ BCE ]]>
			</category>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/?p=307401</guid>
			<description>
			<![CDATA[ <p>Le notizie che arrivano dalla Francia confermano il trend che si era ormai delineato da tempo. In caso di elezioni, il vero vincitore è l’astensionismo. Per Parigi, infatti, si è arrivati al 54%. Ed è proprio da questo dato che bisogna partire per un’analisi del voto francese. Voto che ha portato l’attuale presidente Emmanuel Macron, con il suo partito, ad un crollo che, sebbene prevedibile, non lo era stato in queste proporzioni. Così come, in queste proporzioni, non era stata prevista la cavalcata di Marine Le Pen che, invece, ha più che decuplicato la sua presenza in Parlamento. Infatti l’esponente della destra ha portato da 8 a 89 i suoi rappresentanti.</p> <p>Ma di tutti questo i mercati, oggi, non sembrano interessarsi. Ad esempio, l’Europa non si fa influenzare dalle paure che hanno portato alcuni mercati, tra cui Tokyo, a chiudere con il segno meno. Infatti l’apertura della settimana nel Vecchio Continente parte all’insegna di un possibile tentativo di rimbalzo. Invece l’Asia ha registrato una seduta in rosso proprio a causa delle possibili paure per l’arrivo di una recessione.</p> <p>Eventualità che è stata prospettata da più parti. Diverso, invece, l’approccio in altre zone. <a href="https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/oggi-wall-street-invia-segnali-positivi-dopo-lo-schiaffo-delle-scorse-sedute-ma-le-streghe-sono-in-agguato/">Con Wall Street chiusa per festività a causa del Juneteenth National Independence Day,</a> gli occhi degli operatori sono puntati sugli interventi del numero uno della BCE Christine Lagarde, e del capo economista, Philip Lane. La speranza è che possano fornire dettagli più precisi sul sistema di aiuti per i Paesi periferici.</p> <h2>L’Europa non si fa influenzare dalle paure delle Borse asiatiche e procede cauta ma positiva</h2> <p>Attualmente il pericolo maggiore, con il rialzo dei tassi a volte potenzialmente troppo repentino per alcune Nazioni, è che si allarghi la forbice dello spread. In questo caso l’intenzione della Banca centrale europea sarebbe quella di entrare in gioco nel caso in cui ciò si verificasse. Quindi in corso d’opera e solo in caso di effettiva necessità. Ma la mancanza di dettagli ha finora gettato un’ombra di scetticismo tra gli operatori. Parallelamente l’oro attira l’attenzione degli analisti di Goldman Sachs che rivedono le stime.</p> <p>Per il metallo giallo si parla di 2.500 dollari per oncia entro la fine dell’anno. A dare una mano, tra i vari fattori, anche la crescente paura degli investitori per le difficili condizioni economiche in arrivo. Ma guardando ai mercati, almeno per oggi, sembra tornata la voglia di ridare fiducia alla Lagarde ed al suo staff. Una prova può essere quel +0,37% <a href="https://it.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=TVC%3AFTMIB" target="_blank" rel="noopener">registrato</a> da Piazza Affari intorno alle 11.30. Certamente non un risultato che autorizza l’entusiasmo, ma comunque una dimostrazione del fatto che il Vecchio Continente, peraltro tutto in positivo a metà mattinata, preferisce aspettare che i vertici della BCE diano (o meno) informazioni utili.</p> <p><strong>Approfondimento</strong><br /> <a href="https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/category/il-punto-sui-mercati/">Il punto sui mercati</a></p> ]]>
			<p>TEST Link:<br/>
			<ul>
			<li><a href="www.site.com">text A &amp; 'B'</a></li>
			<li><a href=" http://www.site.com/path/to/place/ "></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://escaped.net/s?aa=bb&amp;cc=25&amp;idx=1&amp;scene=21#wechat_redirect"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://notescaped.net/s?aa=bb;cc=25;idx=1;scene=21#wechat_redirect"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://www.unsafe.com/ac{d}e[f ]\g|h^i,j"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://www.unsafe.com/ac%7Bd%7De%5Bf%20%5D%5Cg%7Ch%5Ei"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://www.unsafe.com/ac%7Bd%7De[f ]\g|h^i"></a></li>
			<li><a href="colon.com/AA:BB&AA%3ABB"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://ru.wikipedia.org/wiki/История_Интернета#СССР-США"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://login:password@www.host.com:80/path/to/q?a=b&amp;c=d&amp;e=00#anchor_to"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://site.com/path+with+spaces+file.pdf"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://site.com/path with spaces%20file.pdf"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://it.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=TVC%3AFTMIB" target="_blank" rel="noopener"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://tmsnrt.rs"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://"></a></li>
			</ul>
			</p>
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid>00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000</guid>
			<title>VIRA_NEW (NASDAQ:LION) Justin Sun Moves 100,000,000 USDT To Accumulate BTC and TRX</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]>
			<p><li><a href="www.site.com">text A &amp; 'B'</a></li>
			</p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/6d6b0-5e3d46b2-62c0-447f-ac3c-6fc5ff1a0fef.png"></p>
			</description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2022 00:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>GUID TEST 2</guid>
			<title>VIRA_title2</title>
			<description>VIRA_NEW_2<![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>1PNG!</guid>
			<title>PNG! VIRA_title1</title>
			<description><![CDATA[<p></p><p><span>8月以来最靓的新股是弘业期货无疑了，自8月5日上市至今仍未破板，累计涨幅高达312%。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/07399-d0cc26e4-3b2c-4e4e-a571-428f6991d5e2.png"></p><p><span class="guru-img-des" style="text-align:center; font-style:italic; color:#999;">（弘业期货上市以来股价表现，Choice）</span></p><p><span>这使得打新人对主板新股充满期待，近日又有一家期货公司冲刺IPO，新湖期货向上交所递交招股书，这家公司背后的资本一时引起了关注。</span></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong><br></strong></em></span></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong>01</strong></em></span></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span>所属“新湖系”</span></strong></em></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span><br></span></strong></em></p><p><span>自古温州出商人，“有市场的地方就有温州人”这句话并不虚，论搞钱，还是得看温州人。</span></p><p><span>新湖期货的实控人便是来自温州的黄伟。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/6d6b0-5e3d46b2-62c0-447f-ac3c-6fc5ff1a0fef.png"></p><p><span class="guru-img-des" style="text-align:center; font-style:italic; color:#999;">来源：网络</span></p><p><span>90年代时，刚毕业的黄伟被分配到中学教书，骨子里流淌的商业基因注定让他成为一个不平凡的人，改革开放的“下海潮”的确走出了一批优秀的创业者，1991年黄伟辞掉铁饭碗，来到杭州通过卖眼镜赚到第一桶金，有了<strong>2万元的本金</strong>，后来又通过炒股、囤积新股认购证、国债期货、商品期货等，短短两三年的时间<strong>赚取了数亿的资金</strong>，身价得以迅速增值。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/496b7-9b356407-b1ba-41c6-bea3-9d0a9ec5acd0.png"></p><p><span class="guru-img-des" style="text-align:center; font-style:italic; color:#999;">来源：网络</span></p><p><span>1994年，黄伟以2亿元的注册资本在杭州成立了浙江新湖集团股份有限公司，<strong>开始进军房地产。</strong></span></p><p><span>他不仅在温州开发了香江大厦，还一举拿下温州瑞安外滩的开发权，新湖集团逐步发展成拥有近20家房地产开发公司的大型企业集团。</span></p><p><span>新湖集团以浙江为基地，扩张的触角伸向了上海、安徽、江苏、山东、辽宁等地，<strong>资本市场上的“新湖系”悄然成型。</strong></span></p><p><span>同时，黄伟一直没有放弃在<strong>金融领域的发展</strong>。目前其控制新湖中宝（600208.SH）、湘财股份（曾经的哈高科：600095.SH）2家上市公司，其中截至2022年3月31日，湘财股份是互联网金融企业大智慧（601519.SH）的第二大股东。</span></p><p><span>此外，黄伟还入股了盛京银行、吉林银行、成都农村商业银行及金洲管道等多家上市及拟上市的金融企业，以及通过直接或间接的方式<strong>参股万得信息、中信银行、温州银行等。</strong></span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/e1b79-9e76d9c3-f874-40a1-af61-3cd0a1c1937f.png"></p><p><span class="guru-img-des" style="text-align:center; font-style:italic; color:#999;">来源：招股书</span></p><p><span>黄伟在投资方面的天赋，在地产圈早已不是秘密，其控制的新湖中宝（600208.SH）曾<strong>以30.6亿拿下绿城中国12.95%股权</strong>，成为第三大股东，一举轰动整个地产圈。</span></p><p><span>除此之外，他的投资版图也涉及芯片、科技等领域，最近上市的华如科技、龙芯中科背后均有新湖中宝的身影。</span></p><p><span>当然，<strong>投资并不总是成功的</strong>，其中黄伟控股的另一家房地产企业新湖创业曾在上交所上市，后因合并事项摘牌退市；此外，新湖中宝背后存在负债高企、曾踩雷51信用卡等情况。</span></p><p><span>2022年，黄伟以<strong>13亿美元财富</strong>位列《2022年福布斯全球亿万富豪榜》第2190位。</span></p><p><span>如今63岁的他即将迎来人生中第四个IPO，新湖期货若成功上市，<strong>或将成为A股第五家上市的期货公司。</strong></span></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong><br></strong></em></span></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong>02</strong></em></span></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span>佣金率逐年下降</span></strong></em></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span><br></span></strong></em></p><p><span>新湖期货的前身为1995年成立的浙江天地期货，2000年新湖集团入股，并于8年后正式更名为新湖有限。</span></p><p><span>截至发行前，公司的控股股东为兴和投资，其持有54%股份，黄伟通过兴和投资、众孚实业、新湖集团、新湖中宝间接<strong>控制新湖期货 91.67%股份的表决权</strong>，为实际控制人。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/cd203-584be868-a176-45d8-9a32-6ddc3e613302.jpg"></p><p class="guru-img-des" style="text-align:center; font-style:italic; color:#999;"><span>（IPO前股权结构，招股书</span><span>）</span></p><p><span>新湖期货自成立以来，主营业务为期货经纪业务、期货投资咨询业务、资产管理业务，并通过全资子公司新湖瑞丰开展风险管理业务。</span></p><p><span>截至2021年12月31日，公司共设立 2 家子公司、1 家孙公司以及28个分支机构。</span></p><p><span>在2019年-2021年度各期货公司评级结果中，新湖期货的评级分别为A类A级、AA级和A级；2021年公司在五大交易所的代理交易金额为14.98万亿元，<strong>市场份额约1.29%。</strong></span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/95634-15d1c614-f060-4e64-a95b-0e76da1c3266.png"></p><p><span>目前，监管机构对期货公司实施以净资本为核心的动态监管措施，其业务规模通常与净资本水平挂钩，2021年新湖期货的净资本为6.86亿元，对应的净资产规模为10.25亿元，在已上市的期货公司中<strong>处于较低水平</strong>。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/13bb6-14160fde-c6b6-411e-a2b1-982c79585db8.png"></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/30b59-0269899b-4b9a-4742-ae32-c59fa94c8e82.png"></p><p><span>业绩方面，2019年-2021年公司的营收由58.48亿元增长至77.60亿元，对应的归母净利润由2429.23万元增长至1.66亿元，业绩逐年增长，2021年公司营收和净利润在行业内分别<strong>排名第44位、第33位。</strong></span></p><p><span>报告期内，公司的经营活动产生的现金流量金额分别为2.66亿元、16.99亿元和10.40亿元，<strong>均高于当期的净利润规模</strong>，可见公司的“造血”能力尚可，能产生持续的现金流入。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/d6012-8ce168e7-0242-47a9-9a71-12f48750d2b6.png"></p><p><span>具体来看，公司的主要收入来源为手续费、利息和投资收益，其中<strong>手续费收入占大头</strong>，其占比由33.42%上升至42.25%，分为经纪业务手续费和交易所减收手续费，后者占比较高。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/8c865-f87eaedd-3441-4b59-9ff6-c77e6e7c4ce4.png"></p><p><span>报告期内，公司的经纪业务佣金率分别为万分之0.117、万分之0.116、万分之0.112，<strong>呈现逐年下降的态势</strong>。</span></p><p><strong><span>靠低佣金抢占市场份额</span></strong><span>已经是目前券商、期货公司最常见的方式，不过值得注意的是，2021年期货行业佣金率普遍有所提升，而新湖期货仍在下降，试问价格战的尽头在哪里？当佣金降无可降，公司的竞争力又在哪里呢？</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/20620-9a5262c9-ec9e-4acc-ad30-871965b56b33.png"></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong><br></strong></em></span></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong>03</strong></em></span></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span>走不出上海？</span></strong></em></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span><br></span></strong></em></p><p><span>新湖期货的总部位于上海，公司在上海地区实现的手续费净收入占比较高，<strong>区域性较强</strong>。报告期内，上海地区的手续费净收入占公司手续费净收入的比重分别为86.15%、88.36%和91.20%。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/a0593-eab03098-2fab-475d-87d3-3e82d8fd5e99.png"></p><p><span>事实上，<strong>地域限制已成为期货公司发展的通病</strong>。</span></p><p><span>一方面，<strong>难以形成规模经济</strong>、降低运营成本，使得公司抵御市场风险的能力较差。</span></p><p><span>另一方面，期货市场本身集中度不足，国内市场尚未产生专注于某一期货细分领域的期货公司，随着行业竞争不断加剧，经纪业务<strong>创造利润的能力下降。</strong></span></p><p><span>近年来，我国资本市场不断完善和发展，2021全年，全国期货市场累计成交量为 72.62 亿手、累计成交额为 579.39 万亿元，分别同比增长20.68%和32.97%。</span></p><p><span>不过，今年以来<strong>内地期货市场成交情况有所疲软</strong>，2022上半年，期货市场成交30.46亿手（单边，下同）和257.48万亿元，同比分别下降18.04%和10.08%，成交量占全球期货市场总成交量的7.9%，较2021年上半年占比12.9%下降了5个百分点。</span></p><p><img src="https://img3.gelonghui.com/315e0-f4c4a2b6-1a0a-4f8e-9686-1bf7fe8a98e3.png"></p><p><span>期货市场易受到经济发展状况、宏观经济政策、利率和汇率波动及国内外大宗商品价格波动和证券市场行情等多种因素影响，<strong>具有较强不确定性。</strong></span></p><p><span>同时，我国的期货公司尚处于业务转型和创新发展的过程中，目前的业务范围和<strong>收入相对单一。</strong></span></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong><br></strong></em></span></p><p style="text-align: center;"><span><em><strong>04</strong></em></span></p><p></p><p></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span>结语</span></strong></em></p><p style="text-align: center;"><em><strong><span><br></span></strong></em></p><p><span>本次冲刺IPO，新湖期货拟发行股票数量不超过12000万股，具体募资额暂不确定，将全部用于补充公司资本金以及拓展相关创新业务等。</span></p><p><span>虽然从某种意义上来说，期货公司并不缺钱，但扩大资本规模是公司发展的必经之路，同时，区域性、业务同质化、高杠杆性等问题一直以来都是期货公司难以跨越的难题，未来新湖期货在金融大佬的带领下将会如何破题，值得关注和学习。</span></p>]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2022 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>3</guid>
			<title>3VIRA_Top 10 Cryptos Lose -50% Since January, Except TRX, Gaining +5%</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2022 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<author:encoded><![CDATA[Michelle Jones]]></author:encoded>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>2</guid>
			<title>2VIRA_new Kusama-backed DEX Mangata X to Launch Bootstrapping on June 8</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2022 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>3</guid>
			<title>VIRA_title3</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2022 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Nikola Announces Acquisition Of Battery Pack Maker Romeo Power</title>
			<link>https://www.valuewalk.com/nikola-announces-acquisition-romeo-power/</link>

	 	 			
		
			<description><p>Shares of electric truck maker <a href="https://www.valuewalk.com/2020/10/hyliion-motors-nikola/">Nikola</a> Corp (<Origin QuoteRef>NASDAQ:NKLA</Origin>) rose as much as 4% by late Monday morning, initially falling about 4% in early-morning trades after the company announced an agreement to acquire battery pack supplier Romeo Power Inc (<Origin QuoteRef>NYSE:RMO</Origin>). The deal is worth $144 million and will give Nikola control over an essential part of its supply chain.</p>
			<ul><li>Nikola Announces Deal To Buy Romeo Power</li></ul>
			<p>The all-stock deal values Romeo at 74 cents per share, representing a 34% premium from the company's closing price on Friday. Shares of the battery pack supplier surged in morning trades on Monday, climbing as much as 38%.</p>

			<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://valuewalkpremium.com/q2-2022-hedge-fund-letters-database-maverick-loeb-southpoint-odey-greenlight-carlson-exoduspoint-and-many-more-last-updated-75/">Q2 2022 hedge fund letters, conferences and more</a></p>
			&nbsp;
			<p></p>
			<p>Under the terms of the deal, Nikola will provide $35 million in interim funding to Romeo, enabling it to maintain its operations until the closing of the transaction. Nikola expects the acquisition to result in up to $350 million in savings over the next four years.</p>
			<p>Romeo Power specializes in constructing battery modules and packs for large commercial vehicles like those manufactured by Nikola. Romeo constructs those modules and packs using lithium-ion battery cells made by other companies.</p>
			<p>Nikola started shipping its electric semis earlier this year and expects to ship 300 to 500 trucks this year. The electric semi maker has been Romeo's largest customer.</p>
			<ul><li>A Lifeline For Romeo Power?</li></ul>
			<p>Mark Russell, CEO of Nikola, said the acquisition will allow the company to speed up the development of their electrification platform. He added that their strong, collaborative relationship with Romeo will enable them to "successfully integrate and deliver the many expected strategic and financial benefits of this acquisition."</p>
			<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/08/01/nikola-nkla-to-acquire-romeo-power-rmo-.html">CNBC</a> described the deal as a "lifeline for Romeo," one of the many EV-related companies to go public via SPAC mergers. Nikola also merged with a special purpose acquisition company to go public. Romeo Power's SPAC merger was completed in late 2020 and valued it at $900 million.</p>
			<p>However, at the end of the first quarter, the battery pack manufacturer had only $66.8 million in cash and equivalents on its balance sheet following over $250 million in losses. Romeo's stock has been trading at less than $1 in the past several weeks, and as interest rates have been climbing, CNBC speculated that the company "may have been running out of options to stay afloat."</p>
			<ul><li>Nikola Pushes To Increase Its Outstanding Share Count</li></ul>
			<p>Meanwhile, Nikola has been trying to secure the approval of shareholders to boost its number of outstanding shares. However, former CEO Trevor Milton has been blocking the electric semi maker's attempts to do that. Milton was ousted after allegations that he had misrepresented details about the company's technology and order book.</p>
			<p>Nikola plans to announce the updated vote counts on the matter on Tuesday when it reconvenes its shareholder meeting. The company said in a regulatory filing on Monday morning that it already has enough unissued stock to complete the Romeo transaction, even if it still lacks enough votes to increase its outstanding share count.</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2022 01:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>2https://www.valuewalk.com/?p=2443156</guid>
			<author:encoded><![CDATA[Michelle Jones]]></author:encoded>
		
	
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:RMO</category><category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:NKLA</category>				
		

		</item>
			
		<item>
			<title>Alibaba Responds To Its Addition To SEC&#8217;s List Of Companies Facing Delisting Threat</title>
			<link>https://www.valuewalk.com/alibaba-responds-to-its-addition-to-secs-list-of-companies-facing-delisting-threat/</link>



			<description><p>Alibaba Group Holding Ltd (<Origin QuoteRef>NYSE:BABA</Origin>) stock slipped about 3% in <a href="https://www.valuewalk.com/chinese-companies-home-where-heart/">Hong Kong</a> after the Securities and Exchange Commission added the e-commerce giant's U.S.-listed stock to its delisting <a href="https://www.sec.gov/hfcaa">watchlist</a>. The shares trading on the New York Stock Exchange tumbled 11% on Friday following the announcement, although they were roughly flat in pre-market trading on Monday.</p>
			<ul><li>Alibaba Added To List Of Chinese Companies That May Be Delisted</li></ul>
			<p>The SEC is demanding that U.S. auditors be able to scrutinize Chinese companies' financial statements as part of the Holding Foreign Companies Accountable Act, which became law in December 2020. If <a href="https://www.valuewalk.com/alibabas-jack-ma-said-to-be-preparing-to-relinquish-control-over-ant-group/">Alibaba</a> and the other foreign companies on the watchlist refuse to allow U.S. auditors to review their financial statements from three consecutive years, the SEC will delist them from U.S. exchanges.</p>

			<p style="text-align: center;">Q2 2022 hedge fund letters, conferences and more</p>
			&nbsp;
			<p></p>
			<p>According to CNN, investors have been watching Alibaba for the last several years. Toward the end of 2020, Chinese regulators cracked down on numerous tech firms, including Alibaba. Shares of the Chinese firm have plummeted almost 70% from their record high. The crackdown and the weakening Chinese economy have slowed many Chinese tech firms' revenue growth, eliminating billions of dollars from their market caps. &nbsp;</p>
			<p>The SEC is threatening to delist foreign companies if they don't allow U.S. watchdogs to review their financial audits from three consecutive years. However, China has rejected U.S. audits of Chinese firms for years, citing concerns about national security. Beijing requires that companies with stock listings overseas hold their audit papers in mainland China, preventing foreign agencies from examining them.</p>
			<p>So far, more than 150 companies have been added to the SEC's watchlist, including Baidu, JD.com, Didi and Yum China Holdings.</p>
			<ul><li>Alibaba's Response</li></ul>
			<p>On Monday, Alibaba said it would comply with U.S. regulators as it tries to maintain its stock listings in both New York and Hong Kong. In a statement to the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, the Chinese firm said it would "continue to monitor market developments, comply with applicable laws and regulations, and strive to maintain its listing status on both the NYSE and the Hong Kong Stock Exchange.</p>
			<p>Last week, Alibaba said it would apply for a dual primary listing in Hong Kong. Although the firm's stock is already traded in both New York and Hong Kong, the latter listing is a secondary one, while the former is the primary listing.</p>
			<p>Alibaba said in a statement that it expects the primary listing process in Hong Kong to be completed by the end of this year.</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2022 01:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>1https://www.valuewalk.com/?p=2443124</guid>
			<author:encoded></author:encoded>


			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:BABA</category>				


		</item>
		 <item>
		      <title>La obsesión de Elon Musk por Marte se intensifica</title>
		      <link>https://es.benzinga.com/2022/08/15/obsesion-elon-musk-marte-intensifica/</link>
		      <pubDate>2022-08-16 09:00:00</pubDate>
		      <author>Shanthi Rexaline</author>
		      <guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
		      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Elon Musk</strong> reafirmó el sábado su <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/trading-ideas/movers/22/07/28085857/elon-musk-says-its-a-fixer-upper-of-a-planet-can-we-live-on-mars">enfoque inquebrantable en colonizar Marte</a> y conseguir que la vida humana sea multiplanetaria.</p>
			<p>“Espero que haya una ciudad autosuficiente en Marte de aquí a 20 años”, afirmó el CEO de Tesla en un tuit.</p>
			<p>Musk hizo estas declaraciones como respuesta a un tuit de los propietarios de Tesla de Silicon Valley, que publicaron una imagen que mostraba tanto los inicios de SpaceX como su estado actual. La imagen iba acompañada del texto: “2022: Cómo comenzó todo vs. 2022”. En el tuit también se le preguntaba a Musk cómo le iba.</p>
			<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p>I hope there is a self-sustaining city on Mars in 20 years!</p>
			<p>— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1558649397856157697?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 14, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
			<p><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>El mes pasado, Musk expresó que la humanidad llegará a Marte durante nuestra vida. Así como la Luna nos unió en 1969, Marte lo haría en el futuro, añadió.</p>
			<p>Asimismo, a mediados de julio, el multimillonario habló de crear una civilización autosostenible en el planeta rojo, lo que significaría ser autosuficientes en cuanto a suministros y no depender de la Tierra para ellos.</p>
			<p>"20-30 años desde el primer aterrizaje humano si el crecimiento de la tasa de lanzamientos es exponencial", señaló el CEO de Tesla por aquel entonces.</p>
			<p>El cronograma supone que se transporten alrededor de 100.000 personas por vuelo y se necesitan alrededor de 2 millones de personas, explicó.</p>
			<p>La semana pasada, Musk compartió una imagen de una nave espacial sobre una superficie roja y la subtituló: "Esto será Marte algún día".</p>
			<p><em>Foto cortesía de Steve Jurvetson en Flickr</em></p>
			<div class="p-message_pane_message__message_label c-message_kit__labels c-message_kit__labels--light">
			<div class="c-message_kit__gutter">
			<div class="c-message_kit__gutter__right" role="presentation" data-qa="message_content">
			<div class="c-message_kit__blocks c-message_kit__blocks--rich_text">
			<div class="c-message__message_blocks c-message__message_blocks--rich_text" data-qa="message-text">
			<div class="p-block_kit_renderer" data-qa="block-kit-renderer">
			<div class="p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper--first">
			<div class="p-rich_text_block" dir="auto">
			<div class="p-rich_text_section">¿<i data-stringify-type="italic">Quieres hacer trading como un profesional? Prueba </i><b data-stringify-type="bold"><i data-stringify-type="italic">GRATIS</i></b><i data-stringify-type="italic"> la </i><b data-stringify-type="bold"><i data-stringify-type="italic"><a class="c-link" tabindex="-1" href="https://es.benzinga.com/newsletter_spanish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-stringify-link="https://es.benzinga.com/newsletter_spanish/" data-sk="tooltip_parent" data-remove-tab-index="true">Newsletter Premium</a></i></b><b data-stringify-type="bold"><i data-stringify-type="italic"> </i></b><i data-stringify-type="italic">4 en 1 de Benzinga España con acciones, breakouts, criptomonedas y opciones.</i></div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			<p><a href="https://es.benzinga.com/2022/08/15/obsesion-elon-musk-marte-intensifica/">Lee el resto del artículo en Benzinga España</a></p>
			]]></description>
			 <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Elon Musk</strong> reafirmó el sábado su <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/trading-ideas/movers/22/07/28085857/elon-musk-says-its-a-fixer-upper-of-a-planet-can-we-live-on-mars">enfoque inquebrantable en colonizar Marte</a> y conseguir que la vida humana sea multiplanetaria.</p>
			<p>“Espero que haya una ciudad autosuficiente en Marte de aquí a 20 años”, afirmó el CEO de Tesla en un tuit.</p>
			<p>Musk hizo estas declaraciones como respuesta a un tuit de los propietarios de Tesla de Silicon Valley, que publicaron una imagen que mostraba tanto los inicios de SpaceX como su estado actual. La imagen iba acompañada del texto: “2022: Cómo comenzó todo vs. 2022”. En el tuit también se le preguntaba a Musk cómo le iba.</p>
			<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p>I hope there is a self-sustaining city on Mars in 20 years!</p>
			<p>— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1558649397856157697?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 14, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
			<p><script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>El mes pasado, Musk expresó que la humanidad llegará a Marte durante nuestra vida. Así como la Luna nos unió en 1969, Marte lo haría en el futuro, añadió.</p>
			<p>Asimismo, a mediados de julio, el multimillonario habló de crear una civilización autosostenible en el planeta rojo, lo que significaría ser autosuficientes en cuanto a suministros y no depender de la Tierra para ellos.</p>
			<p>"20-30 años desde el primer aterrizaje humano si el crecimiento de la tasa de lanzamientos es exponencial", señaló el CEO de Tesla por aquel entonces.</p>
			<p>El cronograma supone que se transporten alrededor de 100.000 personas por vuelo y se necesitan alrededor de 2 millones de personas, explicó.</p>
			<p>La semana pasada, Musk compartió una imagen de una nave espacial sobre una superficie roja y la subtituló: "Esto será Marte algún día".</p>
			<p><em>Foto cortesía de Steve Jurvetson en Flickr</em></p>
			<div class="p-message_pane_message__message_label c-message_kit__labels c-message_kit__labels--light">
			<div class="c-message_kit__gutter">
			<div class="c-message_kit__gutter__right" role="presentation" data-qa="message_content">
			<div class="c-message_kit__blocks c-message_kit__blocks--rich_text">
			<div class="c-message__message_blocks c-message__message_blocks--rich_text" data-qa="message-text">
			<div class="p-block_kit_renderer" data-qa="block-kit-renderer">
			<div class="p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper--first">
			<div class="p-rich_text_block" dir="auto">
			<div class="p-rich_text_section">¿<i data-stringify-type="italic">Quieres hacer trading como un profesional? Prueba </i><b data-stringify-type="bold"><i data-stringify-type="italic">GRATIS</i></b><i data-stringify-type="italic"> la </i><b data-stringify-type="bold"><i data-stringify-type="italic"><a class="c-link" tabindex="-1" href="https://es.benzinga.com/newsletter_spanish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-stringify-link="https://es.benzinga.com/newsletter_spanish/" data-sk="tooltip_parent" data-remove-tab-index="true">Newsletter Premium</a></i></b><b data-stringify-type="bold"><i data-stringify-type="italic"> </i></b><i data-stringify-type="italic">4 en 1 de Benzinga España con acciones, breakouts, criptomonedas y opciones.</i></div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			<p><a href="https://es.benzinga.com/2022/08/15/obsesion-elon-musk-marte-intensifica/">Lee el resto del artículo en Benzinga España</a></p>
			]]></content:encoded>
                </item>
	</channel>
</rss>
