<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Noticias ahora</title>
		<link>https://www.europapress.es</link>
		<description>Noticias de actualidad</description>
		<language>es-ES</language>
		<item>
			<title>L’Europa non si fa influenzare dalle paure delle Borse asiatiche e procede cauta ma positiva</title>
			<link>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/leuropa-non-si-fa-influenzare-dalle-paure-delle-borse-asiatiche-e-procede-cauta-ma-positiva/</link>
			<dc:creator>
			<![CDATA[ Rossana Prezioso ]]>
			</dc:creator>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2022 00:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
			<category>
			<![CDATA[ Economia e Mercati ]]>
			</category>
			<category>
			<![CDATA[ BCE ]]>
			</category>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/?p=307401</guid>
			<description>
			<![CDATA[ <p>Le notizie che arrivano dalla Francia confermano il trend che si era ormai delineato da tempo. In caso di elezioni, il vero vincitore è l’astensionismo. Per Parigi, infatti, si è arrivati al 54%. Ed è proprio da questo dato che bisogna partire per un’analisi del voto francese. Voto che ha portato l’attuale presidente Emmanuel Macron, con il suo partito, ad un crollo che, sebbene prevedibile, non lo era stato in queste proporzioni. Così come, in queste proporzioni, non era stata prevista la cavalcata di Marine Le Pen che, invece, ha più che decuplicato la sua presenza in Parlamento. Infatti l’esponente della destra ha portato da 8 a 89 i suoi rappresentanti.</p> <p>Ma di tutti questo i mercati, oggi, non sembrano interessarsi. Ad esempio, l’Europa non si fa influenzare dalle paure che hanno portato alcuni mercati, tra cui Tokyo, a chiudere con il segno meno. Infatti l’apertura della settimana nel Vecchio Continente parte all’insegna di un possibile tentativo di rimbalzo. Invece l’Asia ha registrato una seduta in rosso proprio a causa delle possibili paure per l’arrivo di una recessione.</p> <p>Eventualità che è stata prospettata da più parti. Diverso, invece, l’approccio in altre zone. <a href="https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/oggi-wall-street-invia-segnali-positivi-dopo-lo-schiaffo-delle-scorse-sedute-ma-le-streghe-sono-in-agguato/">Con Wall Street chiusa per festività a causa del Juneteenth National Independence Day,</a> gli occhi degli operatori sono puntati sugli interventi del numero uno della BCE Christine Lagarde, e del capo economista, Philip Lane. La speranza è che possano fornire dettagli più precisi sul sistema di aiuti per i Paesi periferici.</p> <h2>L’Europa non si fa influenzare dalle paure delle Borse asiatiche e procede cauta ma positiva</h2> <p>Attualmente il pericolo maggiore, con il rialzo dei tassi a volte potenzialmente troppo repentino per alcune Nazioni, è che si allarghi la forbice dello spread. In questo caso l’intenzione della Banca centrale europea sarebbe quella di entrare in gioco nel caso in cui ciò si verificasse. Quindi in corso d’opera e solo in caso di effettiva necessità. Ma la mancanza di dettagli ha finora gettato un’ombra di scetticismo tra gli operatori. Parallelamente l’oro attira l’attenzione degli analisti di Goldman Sachs che rivedono le stime.</p> <p>Per il metallo giallo si parla di 2.500 dollari per oncia entro la fine dell’anno. A dare una mano, tra i vari fattori, anche la crescente paura degli investitori per le difficili condizioni economiche in arrivo. Ma guardando ai mercati, almeno per oggi, sembra tornata la voglia di ridare fiducia alla Lagarde ed al suo staff. Una prova può essere quel +0,37% <a href="https://it.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=TVC%3AFTMIB" target="_blank" rel="noopener">registrato</a> da Piazza Affari intorno alle 11.30. Certamente non un risultato che autorizza l’entusiasmo, ma comunque una dimostrazione del fatto che il Vecchio Continente, peraltro tutto in positivo a metà mattinata, preferisce aspettare che i vertici della BCE diano (o meno) informazioni utili.</p> <p><strong>Approfondimento</strong><br /> <a href="https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/category/il-punto-sui-mercati/">Il punto sui mercati</a></p> ]]>
			<p>TEST Link:<br/>
			<ul>
			<li><a href="www.site.com">text A &amp; 'B'</a></li>
			<li><a href=" http://www.site.com/path/to/place/ "></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://escaped.net/s?aa=bb&amp;cc=25&amp;idx=1&amp;scene=21#wechat_redirect"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://notescaped.net/s?aa=bb;cc=25;idx=1;scene=21#wechat_redirect"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://www.unsafe.com/ac{d}e[f ]\g|h^i,j"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://www.unsafe.com/ac%7Bd%7De%5Bf%20%5D%5Cg%7Ch%5Ei"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://www.unsafe.com/ac%7Bd%7De[f ]\g|h^i"></a></li>
			<li><a href="colon.com/AA:BB&AA%3ABB"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://ru.wikipedia.org/wiki/История_Интернета#СССР-США"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://login:password@www.host.com:80/path/to/q?a=b&amp;c=d&amp;e=00#anchor_to"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://site.com/path+with+spaces+file.pdf"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://site.com/path with spaces%20file.pdf"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://it.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=TVC%3AFTMIB" target="_blank" rel="noopener"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://"></a></li>
			<li><a href="https://tmsnrt.rs"></a></li>
			<li><a href="http://"></a></li>
			</ul>
			</p>
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid>00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000</guid>
			<title>VIRA_NEW (NASDAQ:LION) Justin Sun Moves 100,000,000 USDT To Accumulate BTC and TRX</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]>
			<p><li><a href="www.site.com">text A &amp; 'B'</a></li>
			</p>
			</description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2022 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>2</guid>
			<title>VIRA_title2</title>
			<description>VIRA_NEW_2<![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2022 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>1</guid>
			<title>VIRA_title1</title>
			<description>1<![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2022 01:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>3</guid>
			<title>3VIRA_Top 10 Cryptos Lose -50% Since January, Except TRX, Gaining +5%</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2022 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<author:encoded><![CDATA[Michelle Jones]]></author:encoded>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>2</guid>
			<title>2VIRA_new Kusama-backed DEX Mangata X to Launch Bootstrapping on June 8</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2022 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
			<guid>3</guid>
			<title>VIRA_title3</title>
			<description><![CDATA[Über den Smartbroker...]]></description>
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">CIEA</category>
			<link>link</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2022 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Nikola Announces Acquisition Of Battery Pack Maker Romeo Power</title>
			<link>https://www.valuewalk.com/nikola-announces-acquisition-romeo-power/</link>

	 	 			
		
			<description><p>Shares of electric truck maker <a href="https://www.valuewalk.com/2020/10/hyliion-motors-nikola/">Nikola</a> Corp (<Origin QuoteRef>NASDAQ:NKLA</Origin>) rose as much as 4% by late Monday morning, initially falling about 4% in early-morning trades after the company announced an agreement to acquire battery pack supplier Romeo Power Inc (<Origin QuoteRef>NYSE:RMO</Origin>). The deal is worth $144 million and will give Nikola control over an essential part of its supply chain.</p>
			<ul><li>Nikola Announces Deal To Buy Romeo Power</li></ul>
			<p>The all-stock deal values Romeo at 74 cents per share, representing a 34% premium from the company's closing price on Friday. Shares of the battery pack supplier surged in morning trades on Monday, climbing as much as 38%.</p>

			<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://valuewalkpremium.com/q2-2022-hedge-fund-letters-database-maverick-loeb-southpoint-odey-greenlight-carlson-exoduspoint-and-many-more-last-updated-75/">Q2 2022 hedge fund letters, conferences and more</a></p>
			&nbsp;
			<p></p>
			<p>Under the terms of the deal, Nikola will provide $35 million in interim funding to Romeo, enabling it to maintain its operations until the closing of the transaction. Nikola expects the acquisition to result in up to $350 million in savings over the next four years.</p>
			<p>Romeo Power specializes in constructing battery modules and packs for large commercial vehicles like those manufactured by Nikola. Romeo constructs those modules and packs using lithium-ion battery cells made by other companies.</p>
			<p>Nikola started shipping its electric semis earlier this year and expects to ship 300 to 500 trucks this year. The electric semi maker has been Romeo's largest customer.</p>
			<ul><li>A Lifeline For Romeo Power?</li></ul>
			<p>Mark Russell, CEO of Nikola, said the acquisition will allow the company to speed up the development of their electrification platform. He added that their strong, collaborative relationship with Romeo will enable them to "successfully integrate and deliver the many expected strategic and financial benefits of this acquisition."</p>
			<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/08/01/nikola-nkla-to-acquire-romeo-power-rmo-.html">CNBC</a> described the deal as a "lifeline for Romeo," one of the many EV-related companies to go public via SPAC mergers. Nikola also merged with a special purpose acquisition company to go public. Romeo Power's SPAC merger was completed in late 2020 and valued it at $900 million.</p>
			<p>However, at the end of the first quarter, the battery pack manufacturer had only $66.8 million in cash and equivalents on its balance sheet following over $250 million in losses. Romeo's stock has been trading at less than $1 in the past several weeks, and as interest rates have been climbing, CNBC speculated that the company "may have been running out of options to stay afloat."</p>
			<ul><li>Nikola Pushes To Increase Its Outstanding Share Count</li></ul>
			<p>Meanwhile, Nikola has been trying to secure the approval of shareholders to boost its number of outstanding shares. However, former CEO Trevor Milton has been blocking the electric semi maker's attempts to do that. Milton was ousted after allegations that he had misrepresented details about the company's technology and order book.</p>
			<p>Nikola plans to announce the updated vote counts on the matter on Tuesday when it reconvenes its shareholder meeting. The company said in a regulatory filing on Monday morning that it already has enough unissued stock to complete the Romeo transaction, even if it still lacks enough votes to increase its outstanding share count.</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 01:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://www.valuewalk.com/?p=2443156</guid>
			<author:encoded><![CDATA[Michelle Jones]]></author:encoded>
		
	
			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:RMO</category><category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:NKLA</category>				
		

		</item>
			
		<item>
			<title>Alibaba Responds To Its Addition To SEC&#8217;s List Of Companies Facing Delisting Threat</title>
			<link>https://www.valuewalk.com/alibaba-responds-to-its-addition-to-secs-list-of-companies-facing-delisting-threat/</link>



			<description><p>Alibaba Group Holding Ltd (<Origin QuoteRef>NYSE:BABA</Origin>) stock slipped about 3% in <a href="https://www.valuewalk.com/chinese-companies-home-where-heart/">Hong Kong</a> after the Securities and Exchange Commission added the e-commerce giant's U.S.-listed stock to its delisting <a href="https://www.sec.gov/hfcaa">watchlist</a>. The shares trading on the New York Stock Exchange tumbled 11% on Friday following the announcement, although they were roughly flat in pre-market trading on Monday.</p>
			<ul><li>Alibaba Added To List Of Chinese Companies That May Be Delisted</li></ul>
			<p>The SEC is demanding that U.S. auditors be able to scrutinize Chinese companies' financial statements as part of the Holding Foreign Companies Accountable Act, which became law in December 2020. If <a href="https://www.valuewalk.com/alibabas-jack-ma-said-to-be-preparing-to-relinquish-control-over-ant-group/">Alibaba</a> and the other foreign companies on the watchlist refuse to allow U.S. auditors to review their financial statements from three consecutive years, the SEC will delist them from U.S. exchanges.</p>

			<p style="text-align: center;">Q2 2022 hedge fund letters, conferences and more</p>
			&nbsp;
			<p></p>
			<p>According to CNN, investors have been watching Alibaba for the last several years. Toward the end of 2020, Chinese regulators cracked down on numerous tech firms, including Alibaba. Shares of the Chinese firm have plummeted almost 70% from their record high. The crackdown and the weakening Chinese economy have slowed many Chinese tech firms' revenue growth, eliminating billions of dollars from their market caps. &nbsp;</p>
			<p>The SEC is threatening to delist foreign companies if they don't allow U.S. watchdogs to review their financial audits from three consecutive years. However, China has rejected U.S. audits of Chinese firms for years, citing concerns about national security. Beijing requires that companies with stock listings overseas hold their audit papers in mainland China, preventing foreign agencies from examining them.</p>
			<p>So far, more than 150 companies have been added to the SEC's watchlist, including Baidu, JD.com, Didi and Yum China Holdings.</p>
			<ul><li>Alibaba's Response</li></ul>
			<p>On Monday, Alibaba said it would comply with U.S. regulators as it tries to maintain its stock listings in both New York and Hong Kong. In a statement to the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, the Chinese firm said it would "continue to monitor market developments, comply with applicable laws and regulations, and strive to maintain its listing status on both the NYSE and the Hong Kong Stock Exchange.</p>
			<p>Last week, Alibaba said it would apply for a dual primary listing in Hong Kong. Although the firm's stock is already traded in both New York and Hong Kong, the latter listing is a secondary one, while the former is the primary listing.</p>
			<p>Alibaba said in a statement that it expects the primary listing process in Hong Kong to be completed by the end of this year.</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 01:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://www.valuewalk.com/?p=2443124</guid>
			<author:encoded></author:encoded>


			<category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:BABA</category>				


		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
